Guide to the War Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- World War I, 1914-1918; Series I
  - Lafon Allen Collection
    - United States of America
      - Over There., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0011; 40x60 inches (Box 119)
        Artist: Sterner, Albert. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Speed Means Safety for Our Ships. The U.S. Navy's Need is 7000, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0012; 28x42 inches (Box 119)
      - All Together! Enlist in the Navy., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0013; 43x31 inches (Box 119)
        Artist: Reuterdahl, H.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Follow the Boys in Blue for Home and Country, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0014; 29x21 inches (Box 119)
        Artist: Wright, George. Place of Publication: United States.
      - U.S. Navy - Help Your Country, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0015; 28x40 inches (Box 119)
      - Gee, I Wish I were a Man. I'd Join the Navy., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0016; 27x40 inches (Box 119)
      - Here He Is, Sir., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0017; 28x40 inches (Box 119)
        Artist: Gibson, Charles Dana. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Enlist in the Navy - To Arms., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0018; 27x40 inches (Box 119)
        Artist: Bancroft, Milton. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Navy Now!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0019; 25x37 inches (Box 119)
      - Enlist in the Navy, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0020; 34x28 inches (Box 119)
        Artist: Raemaekers, Louis. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Navy Needs You! Don't Read American History - Make It, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0021; 28x40 inches (Box 120)
        Artist: Flagg, James Montgomery. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Sword Is Drawn...The Navy Upholds It., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0022; 28x42 inches (Box 120)
        Artist: Cox, Kenyan. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Naval Militia Is the Only Reserve of Trained, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0023; 14x22 inches (Box 120)
      - Warding Off a Night Attack, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0024; 14x17 inches (Box 120)
      - A Man In Time Is Worth Nine, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0025; 25x38 inches (Box 120)
      - I Am Doing My Duty. Are You? Your Navy Needs You This Minute, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0026; 14x22 inches (Box 120)
        Artist: Jordan, Clinton. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Keep the American Flag on the Seas, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0027; 14x22 inches (Box 120)
        Artist: Smith, Frank Vining. Place of Publication: United States.
      - For Liberty's Sake, Enlist in the Navy., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0028; 14x22 inches (Box 120)
      - Pull Together, Men. The Navy Needs Us, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0029; 14x22 inches (Box 120)
        Artist: Boonhower, Paul R.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The First Line of Defense Needs You. Enlist in the Navy., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0030; 21x11 inches (Box 120)
        Artist: Shirer, H.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Join the Navy., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0031; 28x29 inches (Box 120)
        Artist: Babcock. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Your Country Needs You. Join the Navy, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0032; 17x20 inches (Box 120)
        Artist: Armstrong. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Extra. Your Country Needs You in the United States Navy, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0033; 20x30 inches (Box 120)
      - Extra. Your Country Needs You in the United States Navy, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0034; 20x30 inches (Box 120)
      - The Navy is Calling. Enlist Now., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0035; 28x41 inches (Box 120)
        Artist: Britton, L.N.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - I Want You for the Navy. Apply Any Recruiting Station, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0036; 14x11 inches (Box 120)
      - Enlist. On Which Side of the Window Are You?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0037; 26x39 inches (Box 121)
        Artist: Brey, Laura. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Father of Our Country Appealed for Soldiers as Follows, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0038; 28x42 inches (Box 121)
      - Pro Patria! Join Army for Period of the War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0039; 28x42 inches (Box 121)
        Artist: Welsh, H. D.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Make the World Save. Enlist Now and Go with Your Friends., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0040; 28x41 inches (Box 121)
      - U.S. Army Develops All a Man Has of Courage, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0041; 29x42 inches (Box 121)
      - Here's Your Chance. Answer the Roll Call of Honor, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0042; 25x41 inches (Box 121)
      - If It Is Worth Living Under, It is Worth Fighting For., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0043; 27x41 inches (Box 121)
        Artist: Gunther. Place of Publication: United States.
      - It's Up to You. Protect the Nation's Honor., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0044; 27x41 inches (Box 121)
        Artist: Scheck. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Wanted - 500 Bakers for the U.S. Army, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0045; 28x41 inches (Box 121)
        Artist: Dewey. Place of Publication: United States.
      - If You Are an Electrician, Mechanic or Telegraph Operator, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0046; 28x41 inches (Box 121)
        Artist: Welsh, H.D.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - I Want You for the U.S. Army., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0047; 30x40 inches (Box 121)
        Artist: Flagg, James. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Columbia Calls, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0048; 30x40 inches (Box 121)
      - The Call of Duty. Join the Army, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0049; 30x40 inches (Box 121)
      - Columbia's Call, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0050; 16x26 inches (Box 121)
      - U.S. Marines - Uncle Sam's Right Hand., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0051; 20x28 inches (Box 122)
      - First in France - U.S. Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0052; 21x28 inches (Box 122)
        Artist: Coughlin, John A.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The U.S. Marines Want You., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0053; 21x28 inches (Box 122)
      - First to Fight - U.S. Marines. Enlist at 24 East 23rd Street., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0054; 42x17 inches (Box 122)
      - He Did His Duty. Will You?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0055; 21x28 inches (Box 122)
      - U.S. Marines - Active Service on Land and Sea., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0056; 28x40 inches (Box 122)
      - Spirit of 1917, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0057; 18x26 inches (Box 122)
      - This Device on Hat or Helmet Means U.S. Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0058; 28x42 inches (Box 122)
      - Be a Sea Soldier, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0059; 30x40 inches (Box 122)
        Artist: Underwood, Clarence. Place of Publication: United States.
      - If You Want to Fight, Join the Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0060; 30x40 inches (Box 122)
      - E-E-E-Yah-Yip. Go over with the U.S. Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0061; 21x28 inches (Box 122)
      - All in the Day's Work. Enlist in the U.S. Marine Corps, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0062; 16x21 inches (Box 122)
        Artist: Gatchell, Charles. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Premiers au Feu means in French "First to Fight"; in Enlish, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0063; 28x42 inches (Box 122)
      - U.S. Marines - First to Fight for Democracy., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0064; 30x40 inches (Box 122)
        Artist: Shafer, L.A.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Halt! Who Goes there?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0065; 30x40 inches (Box 122)
        Artist: Tornrose, Axel. Place of Publication: United States.
      - First in the Flight - Always Faithful, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0066; 28x42 inches (Box 123)
      - Be Up to Date - Be a U.S. Marine, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0067; 18x29 inches (Box 123)
        Artist: Roger, W. A.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Spirit of 1917 - Join the U.S. Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0068; 30x40 inches (Box 123)
      - First to Fight - Democracy's Vangaurd, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0069; 30x40 inches (Box 123)
        Artist: Riesenburg, Sidney H.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - First to Fight in France for Freedom, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0070; 30x40 inches (Box 123)
        Artist: Yohn.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Rally Round the Flag with U.S. Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0071; 30x40 inches (Box 123)
      - For Action on Sea and Land, Join the Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0072; 16x13 inches (Box 123)
      - Join the U.S. Marine Corps. Soldiers of the Sea, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0073; 12x16 inches (Box 123)
      - Do Your duty - Join the U.S. Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0074; 17x26 inches (Box 123)
      - Join Me, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0075; 21x11 inches (Box 123)
      - What Is This?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0076; 20x10 inches (Box 123)
      - Teufel Hunden, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0077; 19x28 inches (Box 123)
      - Tell That to the Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0078; 30x40 inches (Box 123)
      - Marine Corps Week, June 10-16., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0079; 18x25 inches (Box 123)
      - Enlist., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0080; 23x32 inches (Box 124)
        Artist: Spear, Fred. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Second Artillery (1840-1917) Needs 200 Real Men, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0081; 23x29 inches (Box 124)
      - Urgent! The President Has Issued an Urgent Call for 70,000 Recruits, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0082; 28x42 inches (Box 124)
      - Register June 5th. A Great Day of Patriotic Devotion, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0083; 23x55 inches (Box 124)
        Artist: Colen, Authur William. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Britishers, Your Are Needed. Come Across Now, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0084; 28x41 inches (Box 124)
      - Join the Air Service and Serve in France., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0085; 25x37 inches (Box 124)
        Artist: Verrees, J. Paul. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Going - Going - Gone., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0086; 31x42 inches (Box 124)
      - Uphold Our Honor. Fight for Us. Join Army - Navy - Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0087; 28x42 inches (Box 124)
      - American Field Service., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0088; 22x34 inches (Box 124)
        Artist: Nuyttens, N.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - You Drive a Car Here - Why Not a Transport in France?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0089; 19x28 inches (Box 124)
        Artist: Esselen. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Minute Men of Today Are Going to Plattsburgh, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0090; 21x27 inches (Box 124)
      - Are You Trained to Do Your Share?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0091; 21x27 inches (Box 124)
      - Are you Trained to Defend Your Country?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0092; 21x27 inches (Box 124)
      - These New Yorkers Volunteered Last Week. Is Your Name on This List?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0093; 33x21 inches (Box 124)
      - 2,285 New Yorkers Volunteered in One Week, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0094; 33x21 inches (Box 124)
      - Come On, boys, Give the Guard a Fighting Chance, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0095; 22x28 inches (Box 124)
      - Enlist Today in the 69th Infantry. Join the Famous Irish, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0096; 29x41 inches (Box 125)
      - Wake Up, America! Civilization Calls Every Man, Woman, and Child., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0097; 28x42 inches (Box 125)
      - It Calls You - Your Country, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0098; 28x41 inches (Box 125)
      - If Your Country's in War, there Ain't Nothin You Can Do Exceptin', Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0099; 29x42 inches (Box 125)
      - Wake Up America Day, April 19, 1917, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0100; 28x41 inches (Box 125)
      - Britishers, Enlist Today, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0101; 27x41 inches (Box 125)
      - Hit the Bull's Eye! Is Your Name on This List?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0102; 22x33 inches (Box 125)
      - Hoot Mon, The Kilties Are here!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0103; 21x40 inches (Box 125)
      - Enlist in the Army-Navy-Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0104; 18x112 inches (Box 125)
      - Uphold the Tradition of Indiana., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0105; 22x28 inches (Box 125)
        Artist: Ross, J.D.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Join Army - Navy - Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0106; 18x24 inches (Box 125)
      - Volunteer and Choose Your Own Branch of the Service, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0107; 16x20 inches (Box 125)
        Artist: Edrop, Arthur N.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Join Army-Navy-Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0108; 14x22 inches (Box 125)
      - We Need You., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0109; 30x40 inches (Box 126)
      - 10,000,000 Members by Christmas For the American Red Cross., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0110; 41x31 inches (Box 126)
      - [Untitled], Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0111; 31x40 inches (Box 126)
      - Have You a Red Cross Service Flag in Your Home?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0112; 22x20 inches (Box 126)
      - 10,000,000 Members by Christmas. On Christmas Eve, a Candle, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0113; 20x30 inches (Box 126)
      - We Have Joined, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0114; 27x41 inches (Box 126)
      - What Are You Doing to Help? Join Your American Red Cross, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0115; 25x39 inches (Box 126)
        Artist: Grant, Gordon. Place of Publication: United States.
      - They Are Looking to Us for Help, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0116; 56x35 inches (Box 126)
      - Make Good the Promise, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0117; 20x09 inches (Box 126)
      - While Someone Gives His Life, What Are You Giving?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0118; 20x27 inches (Box 126)
      - A Little Starving Child Brought Back to Life Because You Went, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0119; 20x27 inches (Box 126)
      - If You Knew a Day's Pay Would Save a Life, Would You Give One Day, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0120; 20x27 inches (Box 126)
      - Think What You Can Afford to Give, Then Double It, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0121; 20x27 inches (Box 126)
      - The First Three! Give Till It Hurts, They Gave Till They Died, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0122; 20x27 inches (Box 126)
      - The Greatest Mother in the World., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0123; 20x27 inches (Box 126)
        Artist: Foringer, Alonzo Earl. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Keep This Hand of Mercy at Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0124; 20x27 inches (Box 126)
      - Motherless, Fatherless, Starving. How Much to Save These Little, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0125; 20x27 inches (Box 126)
      - Hold Up Your End, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0126; 20x27 inches (Box 126)
        Artist: King, W. B.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - They Fought For You - Protect Them - Help the Red Cross Raise, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0127; 28x40 inches (Box 126)
        Artist: Sesser, W. G.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - If You Can't Go Across with a Gun, Come Across with Your Part, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0128; 28x40 inches (Box 126)
        Artist: Love, C. W.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - 10,000,000 Members by Christmas, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0129; 21x11 inches (Box 126)
      - If You Can't Go Across With a Gun, Come Across With Your Part, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0130; 14x21 inches (Box 126)
      - Won't You Help out There? Give This Week., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0131; 14x14 inches (Box 126)
        Artist: Berryman. Place of Publication: United States.
      - If I Fail, He Dies. Work for the Red Cross., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0132; 28x21 inches (Box 126)
        Artist: McCoy, Arthur G.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - I Am the Red Cross Nurse. I Love My Country. I Love Her Soldiers, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0133; 28x42 inches (Box 127)
      - The Spirit of the Red Cross, A Motion Picture by James, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0134; 19x25 inches (Box 127)
      - [Untitled], Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0135; 28x24 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Fisher, Harrison. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Red Cross Counts on You, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0136; 28x40 inches (Box 127)
      - Second Red Cross War Fund., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0137; 22x32 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Barclay. Place of Publication: United States.
      - The Greatest Mother in the World., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0138; 30x46 inches (Box 127)
      - Read These Facts about Your American Red Cross, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0139; 21x28 inches (Box 127)
      - Ten Million New Members by Christmas, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0140; 20x30 inches (Box 127)
      - The Comforter., 1918; AUS0141; 18x24 inches (Box 127)
      - Loyalty to One Means Loyalty to Both., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0142; 18x24 inches (Box 127)
      - Join. All You Need Is a Heart and a Dollar, 1918; AUS0143; 14x20 inches (Box 127)
      - Universal Membership Week. Red Cross Christmas Roll Call, 1918; AUS0144; 42x8.5 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Fisher, Harrison; Foringer, Alonzo Earl. Place of Publication: United States.
      - I Summon You to the Comradeship, 1918; AUS0145; 20x28 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Mielziner, L.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Have You a Red Cross Service Flag, 1918; AUS0146; 21x28 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Smith, Jesse Willcox. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Have You Answered the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call?, 1918; AUS0147; 28x30 inches (Box 127)
      - The Greatest Mother in the World. Red Cross Christmas Roll Call, 1918; AUS0148; 28x42 inches (Box 127)
      - The Roll Call. A Masque of the Red Cross by Percy Mackaye, 1918; AUS0149; 19x31 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Genthe, Arnold. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Where Columbia Sets Her Name Let Every One of You Follow Her, 1918; AUS0150; 19x28 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Blashfield, E.L.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Answer the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call. All You Need Is a Heart, 1918; AUS0151; 20x30 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Greenleaf, Ray. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Answer the Christmas Roll Call, 1918; AUS0152; 21x11 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Foringer, Alonzo Earl; Treidler, Adolph. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Join the Red Cross, 1918; AUS0153; 21x11 inches (Box 127)
      - Join the Red Cross. Wear Your Button, It is an Evidence, 1918; AUS0154; 21x11 inches (Box 127)
      - Where Columbia Sets Her Name Let Everyone of Us Follow Her, 1918; AUS0155; 56x82 inches (Box 127)
        Artist: Blashfield, E. H.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Joan of Arc Saved France. Women of America, Save Your Country, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0156; 20x30 inches (Box 128)
        Artist: Coffin, Haskell. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Joan of Arc Saved France. Women of America, Save Your Country, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0157; 30x40 inches (Box 128)
      - Save Your Child from Autocracy and Poverty, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0158; 30x40 inches (Box 128)
      - Save Your Child from Autocracy and Poverty, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0159; 20x30 inches (Box 128)
      - Save-Buy-For Victory., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0160; 17x24 inches (Box 128)
      - Help Him Win By Saving and Serving, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0161; 20x30 inches (Box 128)
      - Boys and Girls, You can Help Your Uncle Win the War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0162; 30x40 inches (Box 128)
      - Boys and Girls, You can Help Your Uncle Win the War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0163; 20x30 inches (Box 128)
      - June 28th is National War Savings Day, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0164; 21x32 inches (Box 128)
      - Keep Him Free, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0165; 20x30 inches (Box 128)
        Artist: Bull, Charles Livingston. Place of Publication: United States.
      - They Give Their Lives. Do You Lend Your Savings?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0166; 20x30 inches (Box 128)
      - Buy United States Government War Savings Stamps, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0167; 40x30 inches (Box 128)
      - $5.00 W.S.S. for $4.12, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0168; 13x17 inches (Box 128)
      - Our Boys Make Good Their Pledge. Are You Keeping Yours?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0169; 21x32 inches (Box 128)
      - I Am Telling You, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0170; 20x30 inches (Box 128)
      - Help Them. Keep Your War Savings Pledge., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0171; 20x30 inches (Box 128)
        Artist: Emerson, Jr., Caspar. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Blood or Bread, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0172; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Victory Is a Question of Stamina, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0173; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Keep It Coming, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0174; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Eat More, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0175; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Save, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0176; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Why Loyal Americans Are Keeping the Pledge to Eat Less Meat, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0177; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Sir, Don't Waste While Your Wife Saves, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0178; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Save a Loaf a Week. Help Win the War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0179; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Food Is Ammunition. Don't Waste It., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0180; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Food. Don't Waste It, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0181; 21x29 inches (Box 129)
      - Wholesome, Nutritious Foods from Corn, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0182; 20x30 inches (Box 129)
        Artist: Harrison, Lloyd. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Corn, the Food of the Nation, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0183; 20x30 inches (Box 129)
      - Save the Products of the Land. Eat More Fish. They Feed, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0184; 20x30 inches (Box 129)
      - This Is What God Gives Us, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0185; 20x30 inches (Box 129)
        Artist: Hendee, A.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - War Rages in France. We Must Feed Them., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0186; 20x30 inches (Box 129)
        Artist: Townsend. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Food Will Win the War. You Came Here Seeking Freedom. You Must, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0187; 20x30 inches (Box 129)
      - The Gospel of the Clean Plate. Don't Waste Any Food, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0188; 10x14 inches (Box 129)
      - Save Seed Corn Now, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0189; 20x30 inches (Box 129)
      - Little Americans, Do Your Bit, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0190; 14x22 inches (Box 129)
        Artist: Parker, Cushman. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Cardinal Mercier Has Appealed to the Food Administration, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0191; 21x28 inches (Box 130)
        Artist: Illlion, G.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Be Patriotic. Sign Your Country's Pledge to Save Food., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0192; 21x29 inches (Box 130)
        Artist: Stahr, Paul. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Headquarters Food Conservation. Selection, Preparation, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0193; 20x30 inches (Box 130)
      - America's Food Pledge. 20 Million Tons, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0194; 20x30 inches (Box 130)
      - Don't Let Up. Keep on Saving Food, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AUS0195; 14x21 inches (Box 130)
        Artist: Mora, F. Luis. Place of Publication: United States.